Airmadidi, Indonesian

E-mail

polii.victory02@gmail.com

Phone

+62 822 3848 5543

foto profil

VICTORY POLII

"Student of Klabat University" ABOUT ME

Hi, my name is Victory Polii. I was born in Bintuni on the first of August two thousand (01/08/2000). My genre is male and for my current marital status is single. I live in Airmadidi, North Minahasa, North Sulawesi. I am an Adventist and an Indonesian citizen.

CAREER GOALS

I am currently studying as a student, majoring in Information Systems. I want to raise the level of ability and expertise in my field to prepare myself for the next job field. Then I had the ambition to get a good job that could add quality to myself. I hope to do my best for the job that I will temporarily undertake in order to improve the quality of my workplace.

SOCIAL MEDIA

Facebook

Hatory Polii

Instagram

polii_hatory

<u>Telegram</u>

polii hatory

EDUCATION

2019 - Present

KLABAT UNIVERSITY

Information System

Airmadidi, Indonesian

2018 - 2019

SMK NEGERI 1 BINTUNI

Computer and Network Engineering

Bintuni, Indonesian

WORK EXPERIENCE

2019 - Present

KLABAT UNIVERSITY

Student Labor of Dormitory Departement

Airmadidi, Indonesian

2018 - 2019

ONE THOUSAND MM INDONESIA

Community Service Volunteers

Samosir, Indonesian

2018

SMK NEGERI 1 BINTUNI

computer Laboratorium Personnel and Librarian

Bintuni, Indonesian

SKILLS

HARD SKILLS

• HTML

60%

• CSS

50%

• C/C++

70%

• MS. OFFICE

75%

• JAVA SCRIPT

Λ0/

SOFT SKILLS

• CREATIVITY

80%

• ORGANIZATION

85%

• TEAM WORK

75%

• **COMMUNICATION**

80%

• COMMITMENT

95%